{
    "subject": "resource/Nathan_Oman",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/Brigham_Young_University",
    "human_readable": "Nathan Oman attended Brigham Young University.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9874983429908752,
            "question": "Was Nathan Oman a student at Brigham Young University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9851619601249695,
            "question": "Did Nathan Oman study at Brigham Young University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9772142171859741,
            "question": "Is Nathan Oman affiliated with Brigham Young University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9573394060134888,
            "question": "Name a university that Nathan Oman attended."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9188710451126099,
            "question": "Which university is known to be attended by Nathan Oman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9131479263305664,
            "question": "Where did Nathan Oman attend university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8567450046539307,
            "question": "What is the name of the university Nathan Oman attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7919739484786987,
            "question": "What institution did Nathan Oman attend for his education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7059246897697449,
            "question": "What university is Nathan Oman associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5150780081748962,
            "question": "Is Brigham Young University a place of higher education?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nathan Oman attended Brigham Young University.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5296_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What university is Nathan Oman associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5296_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What institution did Nathan Oman attend for his education?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5296_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the university Nathan Oman attended?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5296_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5296_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5296_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5296_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5296_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5296_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5296_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5296_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5296_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5296_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5296_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe text from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5296/re-ranker-msmarco/48.txt states that the author, who is blogging autobiographically, attended Brigham Young University from 1993 to 1999. This information supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information mentions that Nathan Oman graduated from Brigham Young University, which supports the statement that Nathan Oman attended Brigham Young University."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}